Before I was doing this, I was showing I had another section here to roll.
In order for it to do a wave and piggy back on her head, you have to place those real nice and close to the scalp like that.
Then you're going to go and roll a full head of hair, a full roller, onto her like this.
You're going to take the hair and roll it on the roller.
Rolling it on the roller.
Just rolling it.
Let's get better control of the hair.
You can do this too.
Placing another roller here for security.
Another roller here for the wave.
Smaller roller here pushing it up for the wave.
That will give you like a piggy back effect like that.
It will come out wavy like this.
I was about to finish it and then I decided to show you that you can also finish it this way.